A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Faculty Personnel Actions, 1962-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Faculty Personnel Actions 1962-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/2.911
This collection consists of 3 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access
Access to salary information will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia-2.1-340 ff.) or if permission is granted by the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 August 26.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists of faculty personnel action letters. Topics include elections, re-elections, promotions, leaves of absence, changes of title, special salary actions, resignations, appointments, retirements, selections as professor emeritus, and obituaries.
Contents List
- Personnel Letters--Elections 1990 (Box 1)
- Personnel Letters--Elections 1990 (Box 1)
- Personnel Letters--Election to Named Chair 1990 (Box 1)
- Personnel Letters--Cancellation of Election 1990 (Box 1)
- Personnel Letters--Election of Librarians 1990 (Box 1)
- Personnel Letters--Re-elections 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Re-elections 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Promotions 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Leaves of Absence 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Change of Title 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Special Salary Actions 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Special Salary Actions 1990 (Box 2)
- Personnel Letters--Resignations 1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Appointments 1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Retirement 1962-1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Retirement 1962-1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Professor Emeritus 1963-1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Central Virginia Regional Office 1977-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Hampton Roads Regional Office 1978-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Lynchburg Regional Office 1978-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Northern Virginia Regional Office 1977-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Richmond Regional Office 1977-1981 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Roanoke Regional Office 1977-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Southwestern Virginia Regional Office 1979-1982 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Obituaries 1990 (Box 3)
- Personnel Letters--Clinch Valley College Personnel Actions 1988-1990 (Box 3)